<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>de·con·struct</title>
    <link href="https://blog.aloui.se/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://blog.aloui.se" />
    <updated>2023-10-25T02:13:29-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>thelastinuit</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://blog.aloui.se</id>

    <entry>
        <title>But If It&#x27;s Me Reading The Signs</title>
        <author>
            <name>thelastinuit</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://blog.aloui.se/but-if-its-me-reading-the-signs.html"/>
        <id>https://blog.aloui.se/but-if-its-me-reading-the-signs.html</id>

        <updated>2023-10-25T02:13:29-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    At my age, or any age for that matter, I'm sure people will say it's silly to believe in signs from the Universe, God, or however you want to call it. I believe and follow of them since I was a child. As long as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__video" style="min-width: 100%;"><video loading="lazy" width="728" height="360" style="width: 728px; height: 360px;" controls="controls" data-mce-fragment="1">
<source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/thelastinuit/thelastinuit.github.io/videos/ifitsmereadinthesigns.mp4" type="video/mp4" /></video></figure>
<p>At my age, or any age for that matter, I'm sure people will say it's silly to believe in signs from the Universe, God, or however you want to call it. I believe and follow of them since I was a child. As long as my intuition and heart was in aligned, I always, always follow them.</p>
<p>Of course with time, I learnt that it didn't mean it was going to be a good thing, nor even a bad thing. But it'd be a path that you needed to take in order to learn, or fail to learn, a lesson.</p>
<p>I have made so many great mistakes. I have hurt people deeply. I've been hurt by people deeply. I regret none of it. Some of them became my best friends. Some other, never came back. That's alright. I didn't mean to hurt them and I know they didn't mean to hurt me. That's just the way it is and I'm ok with the logic behind.</p>
<p>And evidently it is intertwined with my romantic way of being. Both are silly beliefs I won't deny that. I love that part of me, though. </p>
<p>I just hope one day she, whoever she is, if there is any, can beat my crazy by doing something crazy herself.</p>
<p>Thus then, I will tell her <em>thank you, I love you</em>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>I Believe In Love</title>
        <author>
            <name>thelastinuit</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://blog.aloui.se/i-believe-in-love.html"/>
        <id>https://blog.aloui.se/i-believe-in-love.html</id>

        <updated>2023-10-23T20:07:21-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    There is probably lots of people who believe that. But in my life on Earth, she is the first person I heard to say that. I also believe such thing but I kept it to myself because I've heard people critize other people about it&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__video"><video loading="lazy" width="694" height="346" style="width: 694px; height: 346px;" controls="controls" data-mce-fragment="1">
<source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/thelastinuit/thelastinuit.github.io/videos/ibelieveinlove.mp4" type="video/mp4" /></video></figure>
<p>There is probably lots of people who believe that. But in my life on Earth, she is the first person I heard to say that. I also believe such thing but I kept it to myself because I've heard people critize other people about it and I got scared. I didn't want to be rejected. I was only a child.</p>
<p>After so many years, I can say it without feeling bad. Hearing her uttering those words vibed so deep in me that it broke me out of my self-constructed shell. After all, it was me who put me there not people's criticism.</p>
<p>Is such thing silly? I will assume it is but I rather live in believing such thing. I have dwelled in other philosophies and I just can't keep doing that. </p>
<p>When I was a child I was such a hopeless romantic and silly. My grandma understood that. She was my best friend. I saw Life with such awe and she did too.</p>
<p>Why did I let society to mold me? Anyway, it is over.</p>
<p>I believe in Love.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
