<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>de·con·struct</title>
    <link href="https://blog.aloui.se/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://blog.aloui.se" />
    <updated>2023-10-23T20:07:21-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>thelastinuit</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://blog.aloui.se</id>

    <entry>
        <title>I Believe In Love</title>
        <author>
            <name>thelastinuit</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://blog.aloui.se/i-believe-in-love.html"/>
        <id>https://blog.aloui.se/i-believe-in-love.html</id>

        <updated>2023-10-23T20:07:21-05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    There is probably lots of people who believe that. But in my life on Earth, she is the first person I heard to say that. I also believe such thing but I kept it to myself because I've heard people critize other people about it&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__video"><video loading="lazy" width="694" height="346" style="width: 694px; height: 346px;" controls="controls" data-mce-fragment="1">
<source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/thelastinuit/thelastinuit.github.io/videos/ibelieveinlove.mp4" type="video/mp4" /></video></figure>
<p>There is probably lots of people who believe that. But in my life on Earth, she is the first person I heard to say that. I also believe such thing but I kept it to myself because I've heard people critize other people about it and I got scared. I didn't want to be rejected. I was only a child.</p>
<p>After so many years, I can say it without feeling bad. Hearing her uttering those words vibed so deep in me that it broke me out of my self-constructed shell. After all, it was me who put me there not people's criticism.</p>
<p>Is such thing silly? I will assume it is but I rather live in believing such thing. I have dwelled in other philosophies and I just can't keep doing that. </p>
<p>When I was a child I was such a hopeless romantic and silly. My grandma understood that. She was my best friend. I saw Life with such awe and she did too.</p>
<p>Why did I let society to mold me? Anyway, it is over.</p>
<p>I believe in Love.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
